

Stefanija Stanković web design engineer

I am a designer and front-end developer specialised in creating beautiful marketing material and developing web templates. I have the ability to work within a team as well as cross-team and I love to work with customers. They offer me guidelines and I give artistic and unique shapes to their visions. I also help businesses, organisations and individuals design modern, interesting interfaces and define meaningful experiences for web and mobile applications. I am a very passionate designer that is always waiting to grow, learn and try something new. I love what I do and I work exceptionally hard, no matter who I work with.

Outside of work, I'm hanging out with my furry friend in Haarlem, drawing, reading a lot of books, doing yoga or baking cookies.

SOFTWARE SKILLS















WEB TECHNOLOGY SKILLS











www.stefaniadesign.com stefanijadesign@gmail.com

EDUCATION

The Higher Education Technical School 2009-2015. • of Professional Studies

Bachelor degree in graphic engineering and design web design

Technical school "Mileva 2004-2008. Marić-Ajnstajn"

Graphic technician.

EXPERIENCES

2016-2018 • "Dynamicsoft" software company

My position was a UI/UX designer and a front-end developer. As a part of a team, I was worked on maintaining WSC Printer, which is the CMS software solution for the printing industry. I specialised in designing and developing nice e-commerce themes. For the design process, I use Adobe Experience, InVision, Photoshop, Illustrator and for the theme development, I work with HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap and Angular2.

"Execom" software engineering 2015-2016 company

I worked on a freelance designer position for 6 months in a team consisting of both programmers and marketing experts. We worked on a campaign for the "KONTEH" fair. I was designing UI for a game/quiz web app for new employees, a logo and other marketing material for that fair. Also, I was hired for the Android Hackathon event and designed promo marketing materials such as posters. T-Shirts. stickers, flyers, etc.

"Creative Tree" web design studio 2013-2014

I finished a 3 month internship in this company. I had the opportunity to design web mockups for the clients. Also, I made progress working in CMS, especially Wordpress, so I learned a lot about designing and developing Wordpress themes.

Freelance 2012-Present

> I am designing promo marketing materials, logos, banners, websites, etc.

"Futura" printing office 2009-2010.

I was working there as a graphic designer for about 6 months. I learned a lot about graphic preparation for printing and started to be more confident working with softwares, such as Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Indesign and CorelDRAW.